Acton, Mass. South Acton Congregational Church records, 1877-2024.
Congregational Library & Archives
Acton, Mass. South Acton Congregational Church records, 1877-2024.
RG5537
Congregational Library & Archives
5.97 Cubic Feet
(6 boxes, 3 flat files)
The South Acton Congregational Church in South Acton, MA began in 1876 as a chapel society founded by the Middlesex Union Conference of Congregational Churches and the Massachusetts Home Missionary Society. In 1877, a Sunday school was started with the Ladies Social Circle following in 1879. In 1891, the church voted to build a house of worship which was completed in 1893 along with the corporation of the South Acton Congregational Church. The church had various periods of renovations and renewal over the years but faced difficulties after 2020 leading to the close of the church in 2024 due to declining membership and finances. The church formally decommissioned in March 2025 with the congregation moving to the West Concord Union Church. This collection contains records of the South Acton Congregational Church's history, activities, administration, and members along with the chapel society, Sunday school, and Ladies Social Circle. The records include minutes, vital statistics, financial and legal records, building records, programs, correspondence, photographs, newsletters, newspapers, reports, plans, histories, and ledgers.
South Acton Congregational Church (Acton, Mass.)
Restrictions on access
Access to this collection is unrestricted and open to the public.The library reserves the right to restrict access to identifying information.
Acquisition Information
Materials were donated to the Congregational Library & Archives by the South Acton Congregational Church in December 2024; 2024-47.
Biographical / Historical
The South Acton Congregational Church in South Acton, MA was started in June of 1876 by the Middlesex Union Conference of Congregational Churches and the Massachusetts Home Missionary Society as a chapel society. Meetings were held in the chapel in Dwight's Block before they moved to the schoolhouse in 1877. In 1877, the church started a Sunday school with the first classes in October. In February 1879, the ladies of the chapel society formed the Ladies Social Circle which was the first of the church's various women's groups that later included the Congregational Junior Guild and the Faholo Circle of King's Daughters. In 1886, the chapel society served ties with the Middlesex Union Conference and Missionary Society in an effort to be self-supporting. Throughout the 1880s and 1890s and various times in the 20th century, the church shared pastors and services with neighboring congregations including West Acton Baptist Church, Acton Center Congregational Church, and South Acton Universalist Church. There were discussions about federating and joining the South Acton Universalist at various points, but those efforts failed likely due to each church wanting to remain in their own building. In July 1891, the church voted to build a house of worship to accommodate their members with construction beginning in 1892 and ending with a dedication and transfer of land ownership in 1893. Also in July of 1893, the church officially and legally incorporated as the South Acton Congregational Church.
In the 1960s, the church experienced a period of renewal with a parsonage purchased in 1960, renovations and large maintenance projects in 1962 and 1963, and a renovation in 1966 of the cellar from a maze of underused rooms into a space suitable for the Sunday school and other functions. In 1978, the parsonage was added on to and renovated. Also in the 1970s, the SACC Movers, later the Mission Movers, began as one of the longest of the church's many outreach and service efforts that characterize much of the history of the church. In late 2000, the "Room to Bloom" campaign was completed with renovations of multiple rooms including the fellowship hall, offices, and classrooms. Another campaign, "Blessed and Blooming", was completed in 2006 with more renovations focused on accessibility in the kitchen, the chancel, and new floors. Entering the 2020s, the Covid pandemic brought difficulties to the church that it struggled to overcome and ultimately resulted in the church deciding to close in 2024 due to declining membership and finances. In December 2024, the last services were held before the majority of the congregation moved to the West Concord Union Church in West Concord, MA. The church was formally decommissioned March 2025, and the building sold in May 2025.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records depicting the history, activities, administration, and members of the South Acton Congregational Church in Acton, MA along with some records from the chapel society and ladies social circle that predate the organization of the church. The records include meeting minutes, histories, vital statistics, guest books, financial records, legal records, programs, correspondence, building and property records, by-laws, annual reports, attendance records, library records, and records from outreach efforts. The collection contains ledgers, photographs, drawings, pamphlets, notebooks, building plans and diagrams, member cards, and newspapers.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into five series with series 3: Auxiliary groups, 1879-1984 and series 5: Church history, 1907-2024 having one subseries each. Series 1: Member records, 1891-2024 is arranged alphabetically then chronologically by start date. The other series and subseries are arranged chronologically by start date.
Series 1: Member records, 1891-2024
Series 2: Sunday school records, 1894-1954
Series 3: Auxiliary groups, 1879-1984
Subseries 1: Women's groups, 1879-1984
Series 4: Administrative records, 1877-2023
Series 5: Church history, 1907-2024
Subseries 1: Newsletter, 1934-2009
Content Warning
This collection includes content and language that may be upsetting or triggering. These records reflect the language and attitudes of the historical period in which they were created; many of these terms are unacceptable today. The Congregational Library & Archives works to preserve Congregational history and stories while acknowledging that sometimes that history is problematic or questionable. We do this to preserve, contextualize, and reflect on the past so that we may learn from it.
This collection contains racist images and language.
Church records and registers.; Women -- Religious life.; Sunday schools.; Church finance.; Church societies.; Correspondence.; Church management.; Newsletters.; Church and social problems.; Church architecture -- Designs and plans.; Photographs.; Church libraries.; South Acton Congregational Church (Acton, Mass.); Spinney, Caroll Edwin (1933-2019)
- Member records, 1891 2024
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records and vital statistics of the members of the South Acton Congregational Church including registers, baptisms, weddings, funerals, membership transfers, member lists, directories guest books, and member cards.
  - Baptism certificates, 1949 1993; 1949-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Baptism forms and programs, 2002 2016; 2002-2016 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Directories, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Directories, 1966 2019; 1966-2019 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Funerals, 1944 2016; 1944-2016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guest book, 1961 1979; 1961-1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Guest book, 1965 1971; 1965-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Guest book, 1971 1985; 1971-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Guest book, 1985 2000; 1985-2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Guest book, 2000 2024; 2000-2024 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mailing and phone list, 1994 2000; 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Member forms, 1952 2015; 1952-2015 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Member list, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Member list, 1991 2017; 1991-2017 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Member transfers, 1891 1964; 1891-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Member transfers and bequests, 1893 1967; 1893-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Separated Materials
    These items were seperated from Register and minutes, 1934-1958 for preservation purposes.
  - Member transfers and lists, 1891 1962; 1891-1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Members recieved, 1949 1959; 1949-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - New member folder, 2011 2013; 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - New member forms, 2005 2014; 2005-2014 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - New member forms and welcome brochures, 2005 2009; 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Officer lists, 1965 1966; 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Register, 1979 1983; 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Register and book of remembrance, 1945 2024; 1945-2024 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Register and minutes, 1922 1973; 1922-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Register and minutes, 1931 1975; 1931-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Register and minutes, 1934 1958; 1934-1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    This volume has items seperated in Member transfers and bequests, 1893-1967 for preservation purposes.
  - Transfer booklets, 1949 2020; 1949-2020 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Transfers in, 1954 2016; 1954-2016 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Transfers out, 1984 2019; 1984-2019 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Visitor cards, 2004 2018; 2004-2018 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Wedding programs and services, 2004 2007; 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Sunday school records, 1894 1954
  This series contains records of the Sunday school including library records, attendance records, minutes, and account books.
  - Sunday school library record, 1894 1898; 1894-1898 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sunday school minutes, 1897 1935; 1897-1935 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Sunday school library record, 1899 1903; 1899-1903 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Sunday school library record, 1904 1922; 1904-1922 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sunday school treasurer's book, 1910 1929; 1910-1929 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Sunday school attendance, 1912 1917; 1912-1917 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Sunday school attendance, 1917 1923; 1917-1923 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sunday school attendance, 1924 1929; 1924-1929 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sunday school attendance, 1929 1934; 1929-1934 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sunday school miscellaneous, 1953 1954; 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Auxiliary groups, 1879 1984
  This series contains records from the various groups and organizations at South Acton Congregational Church including the women's groups, christian endeavor groups, men's club, and deacons. The series contains minutes, constitutions, account books, correspondence, member lists, and financial records.
  - Women's groups, 1879 1984
    This subseries contains records from the women's groups including the Ladies Social Circle, Congregational Junior Guild, and Faholo Circle of King's Daughters. The records include minutes, account books, financial records, member and attendance lists, notebooks, correspondence, and constitutions.
    - Junior Guild miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ladies Social Circle treasurer's book, 1879 1918; 1879-1918 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - King's Daughters minutes and member list, 1897 1901; 1897-1901 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Ladies Social Circle bank book and receipts, 1897 1937; 1897-1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      This folder was seperated from Ladies Social Circle member list and account book, 1962-1965 for preservation purposes.
    - King's Daughters minutes and member list, 1901 1907; 1901-1907 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ladies Social Circle minutes and correspondence, 1914 1927; 1914-1927 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Ladies Social Circle member list and constitution, 1914 1929; 1914-1929 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Ladies society miscellaneous, 1924 1967; 1924-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Ladies Social Circle minutes, 1926 1931; 1926-1931 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Ladies Social Circle minutes, 1931 1936; 1931-1936 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Ladies Social Circle minutes and records, 1932 1967; 1932-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Ladies Social Circle account book, 1947 1968; 1947-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Junior Guild account book and dues, 1949 1953; 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Junior Guild minutes, 1949 1956; 1949-1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Junior Guild treasurer's book, 1950 1954; 1950-1954 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Ladies Social Circle minutes, 1950 1956; 1950-1956 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Junior Guild minutes, members, and correspondence, 1950 1972; 1950-1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Junior Guild dues and attendance, 1954 1964; 1954-1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Junior Guild treasurer's book, 1955 1958; 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Ladies Social Circle minutes, 1956 1964; 1956-1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Ladies Social Circle member list and account book, 1957 1961; 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Junior Guild member list and treasurer's book, 1958 1963; 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Ladies Social Circle member list and account book, 1962 1965; 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      This volume had items seperated into Ladies Social Circle bank book and receipts, 1897-1937 for preservation purposes.
    - Junior Guild account book, 1963 1964; 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Junior Guild receipts and financial records, 1963 1965; 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      This folder was seperated from Junior Guild president's notebook, 1963-1971 for preservation purposes.
    - Junior Guild president's notebook, 1963 1971; 1963-1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      This folder has Junior Guild receipts and financial records, 1963-1965 and Junior Guild receipts and financial records, 1966-1969 seperated for presveration purposes.
    - Junior Guild account book, 1965 1967; 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Ladies Social Circle minutes, 1965 1967; 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Junior Guild receipts and financial records, 1966 1969; 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      This folder was seperated from Junior Guild president's notebook, 1967-1971 for preservation purposes.
    - Junior Guild account book and receipts, 1967 1984; 1967-1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Junior Guild guest book, 1979 1984; 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Deacon's guidelines, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Young People's Christian Endeavor minutes and constitution, 1894 1903; 1894-1903 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Young People's Christian Endeavor roll call and attendance, 1894 1903; 1894-1903 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Men's Sunday Evening Club minutes and by-laws, 1908 1916; 1908-1916 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Christian Endeavor roll call and attendance, 1916 1928; 1916-1928 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Christian Endeavor minutes, 1932 1934; 1932-1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Junior Christian Endeavor minutes, 1933 1936; 1933-1936 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Christian Youth Club minutes, 1937 1938; 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's League account book, 1949 1954; 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Men's Club constitution, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Administrative records, 1877 2023
  This series contains records relating to the administration of the church including financial records, legal records, correspondence, minutes, meeting warrants, annual reports, yearbook reports, building records, account books, by-laws, building plans and diagrams, and reports.
  - Christian education guidelines and programming, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Chapel Society minutes and annual meetings, 1877 1893; 1877-1893 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Building records, 1891 1892; 1891-1892 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chapel Society expense books, 1891 1892; 1891-1892 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Church construction account book, 1891 1892; 1891-1892 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Building receipts, 1891 1901; 1891-1901 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Pastoral and church correspondence, 1891 2013; 1891-2013 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Original building contract and specifications, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Legal records, 1892 1962; 1892-1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Financial correspondence and records, 1892 1974; 1892-1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Certificate of organization, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1893 1901; 1893-1901 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Manuals, 1893 1917; 1893-1917 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Account book, 1893 1920; 1893-1920 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Meeting minutes, 1893 1939; 1893-1939 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Ecclesiastical council, 1893 1965; 1893-1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Clerk's minutes and member list, 1916 1927; 1916-1927 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Clerk's reports, 1917 1959; 1917-1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Meeting warrants, 1917 1996; 1917-1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Yearbook reports, 1918 1946; 1918-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Church committee and annual meeting minutes, 1927 1934; 1927-1934 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bequests, 1936 1957; 1936-1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Clerk's minutes and member list, 1938 1948; 1938-1948 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Reports, 1938 1966; 1938-1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Canvass, 1943 1966; 1943-1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Clerk's minutes, 1948 1952; 1948-1952 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - By-laws, 1952 2017; 1952-2017 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Maintenance and renovation, 1954 1994; 1954-1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956 2017; 1956-2017 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Budgets, 1960 1991; 1960-1991 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Committee correspondence, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Annual reports, 1962 1967; 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Church, prudential, and executive board minutes, 1963 1972; 1963-1972 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Renovation and canvass, 1965 1966; 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Stewardship committee, 1966 1967; 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Church structure and renovation, 1966 2014; 1966-2014 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Yearbook reports, 1967 2001; 1967-2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Pastoral relations, 1969 2004; 1969-2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Annual reports, 1970 1990; 1970-1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Properties committee parsonage expansion, 1972 1976; 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Church profile, 1972 1978; 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Executive board and church meeting minutes, 1973 1980; 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Pastoral relations committee, 1975 1982; 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Executive board minutes and records, 1977 1982; 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Stained glass window restoration, 1983 1984; 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Annual and budget meeting minutes, 1985 1999; 1985-1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Confirmation classes, 1987 2014; 1987-2014 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Executive board minutes, 1989 1999; 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Front stair replacement, 1990 1998; 1990-1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Register of Historic Places, 1990 2006; 1990-2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Annual reports, 1990 2012; 1990-2012 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - Renovation and construction plans, 1998 2006; 1998-2006 (Folder 1)
  - Design session, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Property appraisal, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Memorial donations, 2001 2017; 2001-2017 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Yearbook reports, 2002 2022; 2002-2022 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Constance McFarland memorial donations, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Strengths report and life survey, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Russell Henderson memorial donations, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Our Mission budget, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Capital campaign, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ed Richter, Luke Tolman, and Shirley Goodman memorial donations, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Open and affirming process and certificates, 2006 2008; 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Open and affirming articles and statements, 2007 2008; 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Open and affirming meetings and resources binder, 2007 2008; 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Missions efforts and forms, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Board and church meeting minutes, 2009 2016; 2009-2016 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Pederson memorial donations, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - June and Arthur Tayor memorial donations, 2012 2014; 2012-2014 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Annual reports, 2012 2023; 2012-2023 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Finance and membership meeting, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Visioning, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Exterior painting, 2017 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Peter Alling memorial donations, 2017 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Church history, 1897 2024
  This series contains records relating to the history and activities of the church including photographs, newsletters, publicity, journals, catalogues, correspondence, programs, flyers, histories, and outreach efforts.
  - Newsletters, 1934 2009
    This subseries contains newsletters from the church.
    - "The Assistant Pastor" newsletter, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - "The Inquirer" newsletter, 1955 1962; 1955-1962 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - "Markings" newsletter, 1978 1982; 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - "Markings" newsletter, 1983 1986; 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - "Markings" newsletter, 1987 1990; 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - "Markings" newsletter, 1991 1993; 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - "Markings" newsletter, 1994 1999; 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - "Markings" newsletter, 2000 2006; 2000-2006 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - "Markings" newsletter, 2007 2009; 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Building photos, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Church activities and outreach, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous photos, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, drawings, and diagrams, undated (Folder 2)
  - Photographs, layouts, and meeting notices, 1897 1966; 1897-1966 (Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous photos, 1907 2000; 1907-2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Programs and flyers, 1912 2017; 1912-2017 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - History and minister list, 1921 2023; 1921-2023 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Publicity, 1933 1981; 1933-1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Publicity, 1933 2015; 1933-2015 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Church letters and announcements, 1942 1981; 1942-1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Activities publicity, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Minstrel show photos and publicity, 1954 1956; 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minstrel show programs and script, 1954 1962; 1954-1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, 1960 1969; circa 1960s (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Children's questionnaire reponses, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fair publicity, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chicken BBQ, 1977 1979; 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Reunion Sunday correspondence, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Building and party photos, 1985 2004; 1985-2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Publicity, 1994 2018; 1994-2018 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Room to bloom renovation photos, 2000 2001; 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nancy Taylor visit, 2002 2003; 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Publicity and press releases, 2002 2009; 2002-2009 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Member photos, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Pie baking photos, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Event photos, 2003 2004; 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Youth mission trips, 2006 2014; 2006-2014 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Green congregation awards, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Missions and outreach, 2014 2016; 2014-2016 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Heifer International trip photos, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Prayer request notebook, 2015 2019; 2015-2019 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - SACC movers, 2015 2024; 2015-2024 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Prayer journal, 2018 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Craft catalogue, 2023 (Box 5, Folder 29)